





## WHO AM I?

I'm a B.Sc Computer Science student at Amirkabir University of Technology. I have worked as an Android Developer and Software Engineer (Backend) for several years. I've studied and implemented several Machine Learning algorithms with emphasis on Natural Language Processing and also I'm interested in Blockchain technology and I've been working on smart contracts and dApps. I'm genuinely interested in ideas involving machine learning and blockchain together.

## LANGUAGES

English - proficient Persian - native Turkish - native

## **EXPERIENCE**

6/2021 - Current Blockchain Developer

Self-Employed

I've done research on several fundamental blockchain concepts (AMMs, Oracles, Governance, NFTs) and tried implementing the corresponding contracts from scratch. Currently, I'm working on Solidity(for ETH, Polygon, BSC, ...) and FunC (for TON - The Open Network). Also I'm in charge of documenting and providing series of tutorials for TON platform on tonic. I'm familiar with developing blockchains and worked with tools like Substrate. I've been working on ideas for providing Al and Data services on Blockchain with decentralized governances.

Solidity / Go / Substrate / Rust / FunC / Fift

1/2020 - Current MLOps Engineer

intelliSearch

I've experimented with and researched modern architectures such as Transformers, built a scalable neural search engine for multilingual texts for semantic text search (intellisearch.ir). For an efficient deploy, I designed a Redis-based architecture to enable scaling and load-balancing and used ONNX for model compression. Open-source libraries I developed: (Lite Inference Toolkit (LIT) for PyTorch, Memory Efficient Attention O(sqrt(n)) for Jax and PyTorch)

PyTorch / ONNX / Go / JAX / Sklearn / Uvicorn

1/2022 - 3/2022 Machine Learning Engineer - Intern

UZH - KrauthammerLab

Designed an abstract tracking engine for tracking a machine learning pipeline - artifacts, metrics, logs, and parameters

Python / MLFlow / Meta-Programming

8/2020 - 9/2021 Lead Software Engineer (Backend)

Tray

Managed a Technical Team of 3+ size for more than one year developing infrastructure and applications at Trayl which is an Online Intercity Transportation Solutions Startup. The system is scalable by design and works efficiently under heavy loads.

Node.js / PostgreSQL / Scrum / GraphQL / Docker

9/2017 - 9/2020 Software Engineer (Backend)

Freelance

Worked as Freelance Backend Developer for 3+ years handling more than 8+ projects.

Go / Node.js / C / Redis / PostgreSQL / MongoDB / graphQL, gRPC / Docker

1/2016 - 9/2020 Android Developer

Freelance

Worked as Freelance Android Developer for more than 4 years, completing 15+ Android projects. Used Android NDK to implement interfaces between C and Java for performance-sensitive operations

Java / Kotlin / Android NDK / RxJava / OpenGL

## **EDUCATION**

9/2018 - Current Computer Science Bachelor's Degree

Amirkabir University of Technology

Current GPA: **18.26/20** 

9/2014 - 6/2018 High School Diploma - Mathematics

Shahid Madani 2 High School

GPA: 19.41/20